W. Dean Edwards collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
W. Dean Edwards collection 1946-2002
AFC 1995/015
W. Dean Edwards and Peg Edwards
2619 items.
11 boxes.
71 folders.
25 sound cassettes: analog.
4 sound tape reels: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in.
19 videocassettes (VHS): sound, color; 1/2 in.
1 videocassette (U-Matic).
1128 photographs (44 folders, photographic prints, negatives): black-and-white, color +9 folders oversize, 1 painting.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
The collection includes manuscripts, photographs, sound recordings, and videotapes documenting the activities of a traditional American square and contra dance group, the Fun Finders, from Colorado Springs, Colorado from 1946 to 2002. Fun Finders was organized as an exhibition square-dance group by W. Dean Edwards, who directed the group from the 1940s through the 1980s with his wife Peggy Edwards. Sound and videorecordings of square-dance calling and instructional videos for square and contra dancing are included.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Edwards, Peg; Edwards, W. Dean, 1927-2005
Organizations
Fun Finders (Dance group)
Subjects
Contra dance.; Folk dance music--United States.; Square dance music--United States.; Square dancing--Colorado.; Square dancing--Study and teaching.
Places
Colorado Springs (Colo.)--Social life and customs.
Form/Genre
Paintings.; Photographs.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.; Videocassettes.
Arrangement
Organized by format into the following series: I. Manuscripts, II. Sound Recordings, III. Graphic Images and IV. Moving Images.
Additionally, photocopies of oversize items are cross-referenced to originals housed in Oversize Box 10.
Acquisition
This collection was donated by W. Dean Edwards in 1992. Additional materials were added in 2004.
Custodial History
W. Dean Edwards donated the Fun Finders Instructional and Historical Videos set of six videos to the American Folklife Center in 1993 to update versions of cassettes donated in 1992. In 2004, the Folklife Center received additional materials from the donor, including the bulk of the manuscripts and graphic images in the collection.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Related Material
The Dean and Peg Edwards collection which provides additional serials, audio and visual documentation of the Fun Finders Square Dancing is housed at the Colorado Springs Pioneers Museum. An online collection inventory is available from the Online Archive of Colorado Pioneers Springs Museum: http://www.cspm.org/finding-aidsinventories/dean-and-peg-edwards-collection/
Access and Restrictions
Sound cassettes and videocassettes are stored in the Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division (M/B/RS). Duplication of collection materials may be governed by copyright and other restrictions. The collection is open for research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Collection Concordance by Format
Manuscript Materials
71 folders Boxes 1-3
Sound Recordings
25 audiocassettes AFC 1995/015: SR01-SR05
AFC 1995/015: SR10-SR25
4 7-inch reel-to-reel audio tapes AFC 1995/015:SR26-SR29
Graphic Materials
537 color prints Boxes 4-9
365 black-and-white prints Boxes 4-9
255 prints Boxes 4-9
1 contact sheet Boxes 4-9
222 color negatives Box 4
39 black-and-white negatives Box 4
Moving Images
1 videocassette (U-Matic) AFC 1995/015: MV12
19 videocassettes (VHS) AFC 1995/015: MV01-MV11
AFC 1995/015: MV13-MV20
Biographical Notes
W. Dean Edwards was born in La Junta, Colorado, in 1927. He was first introduced to square dancing in 1939 through Acacia Park community dances in Colorado Springs, Colorado. From 1946 to 1947, Edwards was a member of the Pikes Peak Square Dancers, an exhibition dance group organized by Bob Cook. He began calling his first square dances in the late 1940s and went on to win the Colorado State Champion Square Dance caller contest each year from 1951-1955. In the late 1940s, he began organizing and directing the activities of the traditional square dance group, the Fun Finders, which he and his wife Peggy headed for more than forty years.
Scope and Content
The collection includes manuscripts, photographs, sound recordings, and videotapes which document the activities from 1946 to 2002 of a traditional American square and contra dance group, the Fun Finders, from Colorado Springs, Colorado. Fun Finders was organized as an exhibition square dance group by W. Dean Edwards, who directed the group from the 1940s through the 1980s with his wife Peggy Edwards. Sound and video recordings of square dance calling and instructional videos for square and contra dancing are included.
First organized by W. Dean Edwards in the late 1940s as an exhibition square dance group, the Fun Finders, and its orchestra, the Hoedown-Aires, quickly grew and provided a venue for hundreds of recreational folk dancers in the Colorado Springs community. This collection documents Fun Finders callers and members, as well as recreational dances from the early 1940s and the expansion of the group’s activities beginning in the mid 1950s. Notable dances and activities are organized by event, including participation in choreographing and calling the square dance scenes for the 1978 film, Comes a Horseman (starring Jane Fonda, James Caan, and Jason Robards); dance programming at the Colorado Deaf and Blind School; exhibition dance programming; and a retrospective exhibit of the Fun Finders at the Colorado Springs Pioneers Museum in 2001.
Audio recordings in the collection include eight programs from the Fun Finders Square Dance television show, which aired for three years on the local CBS and NBC affiliated television stations KKTV and KRDO respectively during the 1950s; five duplicate recordings used in the Fun Finders Instructional and Historical Videos; and thirteen commercial recordings of square dance and contra music.
Graphic images in the collection include photographic images from all of the recreational, instructional, and special programming events, including photo images of dance partners and callers. Events #34 and #44, which would have been found in folders 41 and 53, were not submitted with the collection.
Video recordings include one 6-video set, Fun Finders Instructional and Historical Videos, produced by Dean and his wife Peggy Edwards in the late 1980s and early 1990s as a collaboration between the Fun Finders and the Colorado Springs 11th School District. Also included are recordings of square dance events in Bancroft and Acacia Park in the late 1980s and 7-Up promotional commercials, from the 1960s in Colorado Springs, one of which features square dancing with W. Dean Edwards as the caller.
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Finding aid (Box-folder 1/1)
    Information pertaining to the general use and contents of items within collection. Includes media logs and audio video inventory.
  - Correspondence and Fun Finders Group Information, 1954-2002 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Correspondence, General Education, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 1/3)
    Includes black-and-white annotated photocopies of various photographs.
  - Correspondence, Instruction Videos, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 1/4)
    Correspondence between the years of 1995-2001. Includes black-and-white annotated photocopies of various photographs.
  - Correspondence, Thank you cards (Box-folder 1/5)
    A mixture of handcrafted cards and commercially crafted cards, 1988-1993. Inludes black-and-white annotated photocopies of various photographs.
  - Diploma Lists, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 1/6)
    Worksheet of recipients to receive diplomas.
  - Event Envelopes (#1-#51) (Box-folder 1/7)
    Photocopies of original envelopes that contained information where the performances and the instructional classes were performed.
  - Events (#1): Recreational, Acacia Park, early 1940s-1950s (Box-folder 1/8)
    Includes clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH001-PH007.
  - Events (#2): Special Program, Pikes Peak Square Dancers, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 1/9)
    Clippings, promotional materials, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH008-PH023.
  - Events (#3): Special Program, Broadmoor Hotel, 1951 (Box-folder 1/10)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photograph PH024.
  - Events (#4): Instructional, First Basic Class, 1948 (Box-folder 1/11)
    Clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH025-PH028.
  - Events (#5): Special Program, Fun Finders (KRDO-13 show), 1955 (Box-folder 1/12)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH029-PH030.
  - Events (#6): Recreational, Circle Y (local YMCA), late 1940 (Box-folder 1/13)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH031-PH032, late 1940s.
  - Events (#7): Group, Fun Finders Exhibition Team, 1975, 1980 (Box-folder 1/14)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH033-PH092.
  - Events (#8): Movie, Comes a Horseman, 1977 (Box-folder 1/15)
    Newspaper clippings highlighting Dean Edwards and other local musicians providing old tunes and teaching square dancing to James Caan and Jane Fonda who starred in the movie, Comes a Horseman Wild and Free, which was filmed in Colorado. Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH093-PH184.
  - Events (#9): Instructional, Circle Y (local YMCA), 1948-1950 (Box-folder 1/16)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH185-PH0187.
  - Events (#10): Recreational, Fun Finders Festival, mid 1950s (Box-folder 1/17)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH188-PH190.
  - Events (#11): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Heart of the Rockies Group, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/18)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH191.
  - Events (#12): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Los Colorado Group, mid 1950s (Box-folder 1/19)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH192-PH195.
  - Events (#13): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Fountain Colorado Group (1), mid 1950s (Box-folder 1/20)
    Newspaper clipping and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH196-PH201.
  - Events (#14): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Fountain Colorado Group (2), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/21)
    Newspaper clippings, group information, 1 black-and-white print along with black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH202-PH203.
  - Events (#15): Special Program, Fun Finders, Crossroads, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1/22)
    Clippings highlighting the Summer Crossroads Square Dance company.
  - Events (#16): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Pueblo Colorado Group, mid 1950s (Box-folder 1/23)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH204-PH208.
  - Events (#17): Instructional, Fun Finders, YMCA, mid 1950s (Box-folder 1/24)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH209-PH224.
  - Events (#18): Recreational, Fun Finders, YMCA (Box-folder 1/25)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH225-PH227.
  - Events (#19): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, YWCA Clubhouse, mid 1950s (Box-folder 1/26)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH229, PH234-PH242, PH244-PH248. See folder 72 for negatives: PH228, PH230-PH233.
  - Events (#20): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, The Barn, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1/27)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH249, PH252-PH259. See folder 72 for negatives: PH250-PH251; PH254.
  - Events (#21): Special Program, Fun Finders, Colorado Dance Festival, 1986 (Box-folder 1/28)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH260-PH261.
  - Events (#22): News Coverage, Fun Finders, Dance as Excercise, 1985 (Box-folder 1/29)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH262-PH264.
  - Events (#23): News Coverage, Fun Finders, Lincoln and Washington B-Days, 1985 (Box-folder 2/30)
    Newspaper clippings, a copy of Square Dancing, August 1985, along with black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH265-PH270.
  - Events (#24): Recreation, Fun Finders Contra Photographs, undated (Box-folder 2/31)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH271-PH285.
  - Events (#25): Reunion, Fun Finders, Old Tyme Fiddle and Dance #1, 1976 (Box-folder 2/32)
    Newpspaper clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH286-PH300.
  - Events (#26): Reunion—Fun Finders 1978. Old Tyme Fiddle and Dance #2, 1978 (Box-folder 2/33)
    Newpspaper clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH301-PH319.
  - Events (#27): Reunion, Fun Finders Old Tyme Fiddle and Dance #3, 1979 (Box-folder 2/34)
    Correspondence, clippings, reunion planning, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH320-PH332.
  - Events (#28): Reunion, Fun Finders Old Tyme Fiddle and Dance #4, 1980 (Box-folder 2/35)
    Correspondence, newsppaper clippings, reunion information, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH333-PH353.
  - Events (#29): Reunion, Fun Finders Old Tyme Fiddle and Dance #5, 1981 (Box-folder 2/36)
    Newspaper clippings, reunion information, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH354-PH391.
  - Events (#30): Exhibit, Fun Finders, Swing Your Partner, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2/37)
    Newspaper clippings, exhibit information, black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH392-PH399.
  - Events (#31): Special Program, Fun Finders, Pioneer Museum Exhibit Collection, 2001 (Box-folder 2/38)
    Event flyers and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH400-PH409.
  - Events (#32): Instructional, Fun Finders, 1st Christian Church, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2/39)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH410-PH428.
  - Events (#33): Special Program, Country’s Reminisce Hitch, May 14, 1994 (Box-folder 2/40)
    Newspaper clippings, event information, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH429-PH464.
  - Events (#34): Not received (Box-folder 2/41)
    Event not submitted by donor.
  - Events (#35): Callers/Instructors, Fun finders (Box-folder 2/42)
    Newspaper clippings, event information, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs, PH465-PH500, from the 1940’s, 1958, 1978 and undated.
  - Events (#36): Bands/Groups/Orchestras, Fun Finders (Box-folder 2/43)
    Clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs, PH501-PH534, from the 1940s, 1950s, 1978, 1980s, and 2002.
  - Events (#37): Special Program, Mall of the Bluffs Promotion, August 1977 (Box-folder 2/44)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH535-PH543.
  - Events (#38): Special Program, Colorado Deaf and Blind School, 1948 (Box-folder 2/45)
    Clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH544-PH548.
  - Events (#39): Special Program, East/West Sharing, 1979 (Box-folder 2/46)
    Correspondence, clippings, event information, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH549-PH552.
  - Events (#40): Recreational, Fun Finders, 1979-1999 (Box-folder 2/47)
    Clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH553-PH585.
  - Events (#41): Recreational, Fun Finders, 1979 (Box-folder 2/48)
    Correspondence, clippings, event information, and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH586-PH594.
  - Events (#42): Informational, Letters 1954-1997 (Box-folder 2/49)
    Correspondence from various organizations and individuals thanking the Fun Finders for their participation in events.
  - Events (#43): Informational, Music Book and Orchestra (1 of 3), 1954-1997 (Box-folder 2/50)
    Bound 9 1⁄2 x 7 1⁄2 48-page Orchestra Roll Book.
  - Events (#43): Informational, Music Book and Orchestra (2 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 2/51)
    Orchestra and Auditions. (loose leaf notes)
  - Events (#43): Informational, Music Book and Orchestra (3 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 2/52)
    Band Member Contacts.
  - Events (#44): Not received (Box-folder 2/53)
  - Events (#45): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Madison Elementary School, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 2/54)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH595-PH598.
  - Events (#46): Recreational, Fun Finders, Holmes Jr. High School, Undated (Box-folder 2/55)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH599-PH606.
  - Events (#47): Recreational, Fun Finders, Penrose Hospital, Undated (Box-folder 2/56)
    Clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH607-PH609.
  - Events (#48): Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders, Elderhostel Programs, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 3/57)
    Correspondence, event information, handouts, participant lists, and black and white annotated photocopies of photographs PH610-PH629.
  - Events (#49): Special Program, Territory Days, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 3/58)
    Clippings and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH630-PH638.
  - Events (#50): Special Programs, Fun Finders, 1948, 1977-1979, 1982, 1988 (Box-folder 3/59)
    Includes clippings and photographs PH639-PH670 for the following events: Broadmoor Hotel (1948); Home and Garden Show (1977); El Paso City Democratic Party (1977); National Campers and Hikers Association (1978); Daniels’ Motor Special (1979); Senior Citizens Crime Prevention Fair; National Association of Retired Federal Employees National Convention (1982); White House Ranch Special (1988); Western National Bank Special.
  - Events (#51): Callers, Fun Finders, 1948, 1959, 1978 and undated (Box-folder 3/60)
    Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH671-PH685.
  - Fun Finders Advertisements, 1959 (Box-folder 3/61)
    Telegraph and black-and-white print PH722.
  - Fun Finders Information, 1940-1995 (Box-folder 3/62)
    Clippings, handouts and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH723-PH747.
  - Information packet, Dean Edwards (Box-folder 3/63)
    Information pertaining to Dean Edwards.
  - Information packet, Dean and Peg Edwards (Box-folder 3/64)
    Information pertaining to the activites of the Fun Finders including certificates, articles and proposal to the hall of fame.
  - News Clippings, 1953-1999 (Box-folder 3/65)
  - Programs, 1950, 1955 and undated (Box-folder 3/66)
  - Published Materials (Box-folder 3/67)
    Two booklets: An Architectural Walking Tour of Colorado Springs: A self guided journey through history, The Caller/Teacher Manual, accompanied by clippings of articles and black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH748-PH756.
  - Song Transcriptions (1/3) (Box-folder 3/68)
    Song notations and lyrics.
  - Song Transcriptions (2/3) (Box-folder 3/69)
  - Song Transcriptions (3/3) (Box-folder 3/70)
    DC and E Songbook, 2 copies [unpublished].
  - Photocopies of the content information from the reel to reel tapes boxes, AFC 1995/015: SR006-SR09 (Box-folder 3/71)
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - Audiocassettes
    - Elementary Fundamentals of Square Dancing (1/2), AFC 1995/015: SR01
    - Elementary Fundamentals of Square Dancing (2/2), AFC 1995/015: SR02
    - Elementary Fundamentals, AFC 1995/015: SR03
    - Fundamentals II, (1/2), AFC 1995/015: SR04
    - Fundamentals II, (2/2), AFC 1995/015: SR05
    - Early American Traditional Folk Dance: Henry Ford Era, AFC 1995/015: SR06
    - Early American Traditional Folk Dance: Western Cowboy; Pappy Shaw Era, AFC 1995/015: SR07
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV, program 1 and 2 March 11, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR08
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV, program 3 and 4 March 25, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR09
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV, program 5 and 6 April 8, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR10
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV, program 7 and 8 April 22, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR11
    - Fun Finders No. 1-2, AFC 1995/015: SR12
      1. Pretty Lady 2. Varsouvianna 3. Skaters Waltz
    - Fun Finders No. 1, AFC 1995/015: SR13
      1. Pretty Lady (duplicate of SR10)
    - Fun Finders No. 2, AFC 1995/015: SR14
      1. Varsouvianna 2. Skaters Waltz (duplicates of SR10)
    - Fun Finders No. 1, AFC 1995/015: SR15
      1. Varsouvianna (version 2)
    - Fun Finders No. 2, AFC 1995/015: SR16
      1. Varsouvianna (version 3)
    - Fun Finders No. 4, AFC 1995/015: SR17
      1. Skaters Waltz (version 2)
    - Contra Lamp/Lady- Extended, AFC 1995/015: SR18
      (2 alternating songs, 7 alternations)
    - Contra Lamp/Lady- Extended, AFC 1995/015: SR19
      (2 alternating songs, 3 alternations; duplicate of SR16)
    - Contra, AFC 1995/015: SR20
      Callison Hall Jig’
    - Contra, AFC 1995/015: SR21
      ‘Joy Waltz Medley’
    - ‘Oxford Minuet Waltz’, AFC 1995/015: SR22
    - ‘Tennessee Waltz’ and ‘Oh Suzanna’, AFC 1995/015: SR23
    - ‘Ole Tyme Fiddle’, AFC 1995/015: SR24
      (repeat recording, 13 repetitions)
    - ‘Boil the Cabbage’, AFC 1995/015: SR25
  - 7-inch reel-to-reel audio tapes
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV: 1-2 1950, September 19, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR26
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV: 3-4 1950, October 3, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR27
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV: 5-6 1950, October 10, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR28
    - Fun Finders KRDO-TV: 7-8 1950, October 24, 1955, AFC 1995/015: SR29
- Series III: Graphic Images
  - Negatives
    - Events, AFC 1995/015: PH002; AFC 1995/015: PH007; AFC 1995/015: PH029 (copy negative); AFC 1995/015: PH122-PH141; AFC 1995/015: PH142-161; AFC 1995/015: PH162-PH181; AFC 1995/015: PH182-184; AFC 1995/015: PH196; AFC 1995/015: PH197-PH199; PH201; AFC 1995/015: PH202; AFC 1995/015: PH209-210; AFC 1995/015: PH228-PH233; AFC 1995/015: PH239-PH243; AFC 1995/015: PH250-PH252; AFC 1995/015: PH253-PH254; AFC 1995/015: PH563-PH578; AFC 1995/015: PH677; PH686-PH689; AFC 1995/015: PH694-PH707; AFC 1995/015: PH708-PH720; AFC 1995/015: PH797-PH800; AFC 1995/015: PH843-PH867; AFC 1995/015: PH888-PH901; AFC 1995/015: PH913-PH925; AFC 1995/015: PH926-PH937; AFC 1995/015: PH962-PH985; AFC 1995/015: PH1092-1100; AFC 1995/015: PH1101-1119 (Box-folder 4/72)
  - Prints
    - Events (#1 - #3), 1940s-1950s, 20 black-and-white and 2 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH001-024 (Box-folder 4/73)
    - Events (#4 - #6) 1948, 1940’s, undated, 54 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PPH025 - PH032 (Box-folder 4/74)
    - Events (#7), undated, 54 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH033 - PH092 (Box-folder 4/75)
    - Events (#8), undated, 16 black-and-white and 11 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH093 - PH184 (Box-folder 4/76)
    - Events (#9 - #16), 1948-1950, 1957-1958, 1979 and undated, 17 black-and-white prints and 1 color print; AFC 1995/015: PH185 - PH208 (Box-folder 4/77)
    - Events (#17 - #18), undated, 14 black-and-white prints; AFC 1995/015: PH209 - PH227 (Box-folder 5/78)
    - Events (#19 - #23), 1984 and undated, 34 black-and-white prints; AFC 1995/015: PH228 - PH270 (Box-folder 5/79)
    - Events (#24 - #26), 1976, 1978, 1993 1994 and undated, 17 black-and-white and 28 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH271 - PH319 (Box-folder 5/80)
    - Events (#27), 1976 and undated, 13 black-and-white; AFC 1995/015: PH320 - PH332 (Box-folder 5/81)
    - Events (#28), 1980 and undated, 21 black-and-white; AFC 1995/015: PH333 - PH353 (Box-folder 5/82)
    - Events (#29), 1981 and undated, 16 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH354 - PH391 (Box-folder 6/83)
    - Events (#30 - #31), 2001-2002 and undated, 18 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH392 - PH409 (Box-folder 6/84)
    - Events (#32), undated, 14 black-and-white and 5 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH410 - PH428 (Box-folder 6/85)